export const data = [
    {
      question: "Falling Asleep*?",
      option1: "I never take longer than 30 minutes.",
      option2: "I take at least 30 minutes to fall asleep, less than half the time.",
      option3: "I take at least 30 minutes to fall asleep, more than half the time.",
      option4: "I take more than 60 minutes to fall asleep, more than half the time.",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Sleep During the Night*?",
      option1: "I do not wake up at night.",
      option2: "I have a restless, light sleep with a few brief awakenings each night.",
      option3: "I wake up at least once a night, but I go back to sleep easily.",
      option4: "I awaken more than once a night and stay awake for 20 minutes or more, more than half the time.",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: " Waking Up Too Early?",
      option1: "Most of the time, I awaken no more than 30 minutes before I need to get up.",
      option2: "More than half the time, I awaken more than 30 minutes before I need to get up. ",
      option3: "I almost always awaken at least 1 hour or so before I need to, but I go back to sleep eventually.",
      option4: "I awaken at least 1 hour before I need to, and can’t go back to sleep.",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Sleeping Too Much*",
      option1: "I sleep no longer than 7-8 hours/night, without napping during the day",
      option2: "I sleep no longer than 10 hours in a 24-hour period including naps.",
      option3: "I sleep no longer than 12 hours in a 24-hour period including naps",
      option4: "I sleep longer than 12 hours in a 24-hour period including naps.",
      ans: 4 ,
    },
  
    {
      question: "View of Myself",
      option1: "I see myself as equally worthwhile and deserving as other people.",
      option2: "I am more self-blaming than usual.",
      option3: "I largely believe that I cause problems for others.",
      option4: "I think almost constantly about major and minor defects in my life.",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: " General Interest*",
      option1: "There is no change from usual in how interested I am in other people or activities.",
      option2: "I notice that I am less interested in people or activities.",
      option3: "I notice that I am more interested in people or activities",
      option4: "I have virtually no interest in formerly pursued activities",
      ans: 4,
    },
  
    {
      question: " Energy Level*",
      option1: "There is no change in my usual level of energy.",
      option2: "I really cannot carry out most of my usual daily activities because I just don’t have the energy.",
      option3: "I have to make a big effort to start or finish my usual daily activities (for example, shopping, homework).",
      option4: "I get tired more easily than usual.",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: " Feeling Restles*",
      option1: "I do not feel restless.",
      option2: "I’m often fidgety, wringing my hands, or need to shift how I am sitting..",
      option3: "At times, I am unable to stay seated and need to pace around.",
      option4: "I have virtually no interest in formerly pursued activities",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Feeling Slowed Down**",
      option1: "I am often unable to respond to questions without extreme effort..",
      option2: "It takes me several seconds to respond to most questions and I am sure my thinking is slowed..",
      option3: "I find that my thinking is slowed down or my voice sounds dull or flat.",
      option4: "I think, speak, and move at my usual rate of speed",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Weight",
      option1: "I have not had a change in my weight.",
      option2: "I've lost weight.",
      option3: "I've gained weight.",
      option4: "Weight fluctuations throughout the year",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Behavioral Changes",
      option1: "Not at all",
      option2: "Occasionally",
      option3: "Often",
      option4: "Always",
      ans: 4,
    },
  ];